Tanner Bacon

Orem, UT, 84058 🏫 (801) 919 - 9071 TannerBacon20@gmail.com

✓ BusinessWithBacon.com

Hard working Information Systems student with an aptitude for creating technological solutions for unstructured business problems as demonstrated through success in diverse work experience and academic success. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of Information Systems and Security to meet the strategic goals of Pluralsight.

Skills

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

- Server Setup and Administration •
- Basic Network Security

COMPUTER SCIENCE

- Linux Systems / Virtual Machines C++, JS, Python, SQL, HTML, CSS
 - Systems Life Development Cycle
 - Logical and Analytical Thinking
- Fundamentals of Cloud Platforms Full-Stack Web Programming

PEOPLE AND ORGANIZATIONS

- **Project Management**
- Organizational Skills
- Attention to Detail
- Insatiably Curious Learner

Experience

JUNE 2021 - PRESENT

Marketing and Analytics Associate / Education Services LLC, Draper UT

- Manage and maintain firewalls and DNS servers for multiple Department of Defense webpages.
- Test the security of Department of Defense webpages by attempting VPN logins from invalid locations.
- Analyze extensive Google Dataflow Analytics to draw meaningful conclusions that have tripled web traffic.

JUNE 2021 – SEPTEMBER 2021

QA Engineer Intern / SuperLumin Networks, Sandy UT

- Collaborated with a team utilizing software methodologies and processes to create python scripts that automated over 200 J-Meter and other server speed tests.
- Found and reported incidents collected and logged in 10 personally assigned Linux virtual machines.

MAY 2015-DECEMBER 2017 AND JANUARY 2020 - MAY 2021

Point of Sales System Manager / Bike Peddler, American Fork & Lehi UT

- Wrote scripts to automate spreadsheets and track changes in inventory sales orders, and warranty claims for over 35,000 items of inventory from over 500 vendors.
- Created and documented system procedures such as updating accounts payable and receivable.

JANUARY 2018 – JANUARY 2020

Religious Service Volunteer / The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints, Rome Italy

Lead and followed up with teams of volunteers efficiently to increase regional goals and accurately track the resulting influx of information using purpose-built spreadsheets for data collection.

Education

BS Info. Systems, Security & Forensics Program, CS Minor / Brigham Young University, Provo UT

- **GPA:** 3.94
- **Expected Graduation:** May 2023
- Golden Key and Phi Eta Sigma Honor Societies.
- Related Coursework: Programming in C++ and JavaScript. Database Design and Development. Web Programming, Server Admin in AWS, and Linux VM.

Tanner Bacon

- n Orem, UT, 84057
- **(801)-919-9071**
- tannerbacon20@gmail.com
- BusinessWithBacon.com

REFERENCES

Steve Klingler / CEO and Chairman

Education Services LLC 392 East 12300 South Draper, UT, 84020

+1(801)-910-5222 | steve@edsvcs.com

Marketing Associate and Web Developer

Marketing Associate and Web Developer for CEO and Chairman, Steve Klingler, at Education Services LLC from June 2021 – Present.

Grant Johnson / QA Manager

SuperLumin Networks 9683 South 500 West Sandy, Utah, 84070 +1(801) 999-0709 |gjohnson@superlumin.com

QA Engineer Intern

QA Engineer intern under Quality Assurance Engineer Manager, Grant Johnson, at SuperLumin Networks from June 2021 – Present.

Parrish Pontious / Senior Manager and Co-Owner

Bike Peddler
3600 Ashton Blvd
Lehi, UT, 84043
+1(801) 735-2697 | parrish@bikepeddlerutah.com

Information Systems Manager

Information Systems Manager for Senior Manager and Co-Owner, Parrish Pontious, at Bike Peddler from January 2020 – May 2021.

Michael Pickerd / Rome Area President

The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints Piazza Monte Gemma, 9 00141 Roma RM, Italy +1(832) 771 - 5799 | mikepickerd@gmail.com

Regional Leadership

Regional Leader for Rome Area President Mike Pickerd, at the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints from January 2018 – January 2020.

ADDITIONAL REFERENCES

Devin Jones / Service Manager and Co-Worker. Bike Peddler +1(801) 875-3382

Steven Fillmore / Local Volunteer Leadership Coordinator +1(801) 386-3508 | <u>steven2fillmore@gmail.com</u>

Alexander Banning / The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints +1(408) 598-5262